{
    "id": "47ddb4ab5e3a48d89d8574e94279d2f5",
    "title": "Personal Pronouns Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I earn as much as …………………….. does.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "he",
                "him",
                "his"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "James and ……………………… were present at the venue.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "I",
                "me",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Can you sing as well as …………………?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "she",
                "her"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Will you wait for Jane and …………………..?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "I",
                "me"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "You know that as well as ………………………",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "I",
                "me"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Between you and …………………. there are few secrets.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "I",
                "me"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "We are not as rich as …………………………",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "they",
                "them"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "John is as old as ………………………….. am.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "I",
                "me"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "He is known to my father and ………………………….",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "I",
                "me"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "She is as good as ……………………….",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "he",
                "him"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        }
    ]
}